<!-- Plugin Configuration File. Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <!-- Unique identifier of the plugin. It should be FQN. It cannot be changed between the plugin versions. -->
    <id>com.dev.gear</id>

    <!-- Public plugin name should be written in Title Case.
         Guidelines: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/marketplace/plugin-overview-page.html#plugin-name -->
    <name>ConvertClassFields</name>

    <!-- A displayed Vendor name or Organization ID displayed on the Plugins Page. -->
    <vendor email="1397100450@qq.com">DevGear</vendor>

    <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>ConvertClassFieldsAction: Streamline Java Class Field Conversion</h1>

        <p>ConvertClassFieldsAction is a powerful IntelliJ IDEA plugin designed to enhance Java development productivity. It offers a seamless way to convert fields between different Java classes, saving time and reducing errors in your code.</p>

        <h2>Key features:</h2>
        <ol>
            <li>Smart Class Search: Quickly find and select target classes using an intuitive search interface.</li>
            <li>Intelligent Field Mapping: Automatically map fields between source and target classes based on name and type.</li>
            <li>Getter/Setter Generation: Automatically generate setter calls with corresponding getter methods.</li>
            <li>Code Insertion: Insert the generated code at the cursor position with proper formatting.</li>
            <li>Customizable Naming: Allow developers to customize variable names for better code readability.</li>
        </ol>

        <h2>How to use:</h2>
        <ol>
            <li>Select a variable of a class type in your Java code.</li>
            <li>Right-click and choose the "Convert Class Fields" option from the context menu, or use the shortcut Ctrl+Shift+C.</li>
            <li>In the class chooser dialog, search for and select the target class you want to convert to.</li>
            <li>Enter the variable names for the source and target objects in the input dialog.</li>
            <li>The plugin will generate and insert the conversion code below your cursor.</li>
        </ol>

        <p>DevGear simplifies the process of transferring data between objects, making your Java development workflow more efficient and error-free. With just a few clicks, you can generate clean, properly formatted code for object conversion, saving time and reducing the risk of errors in manual field mapping.</p>
        ]]>
    </description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>

    <!-- Extension points defined by the plugin.
         Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-extension-points.html -->
    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">

    </extensions>
    <actions>
        <action id="Convert Class Fields" class="com.dev.gear.ConvertClassFieldsAction"
                text="Convert Class Fields" description="Generate set all fields">
            <add-to-group group-id="GenerateGroup" anchor="last"/>

            <!-- 这里配置快捷键 -->
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="ctrl shift C"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>